# Juan E. Peña Mendoza

+57 3186788907

juan.pena@solvoglobal.com

Bogotá, Colombia

Bilingual recruiter graduated from Psychology and currently studying a Master in Sports Psychology, capable of using investigation techniques to collect and analyze data also profiling and filtering candidates according to specific parameters. On top of that I am very adaptable, with great communication skills, problem solving and willing to assume leadership. Beyond that I have experience multi-tasking with Microsoft Office packages, while developing strategies to filter and organize information through different sources

## **EDUCATION**

Master in Sports Psycholohy 2022- Currently

ESNECA Business School

Psychology Degree 2017-2022

Universidad El Bosque.

Bachelor's Degree 2016

Colegio Franciscano del Virrey Solís.

# **EXPERIENCE**

# Bilingual Recruiter Jul 2022 - Currently

Solvo Global
Supporting processes of recruitment and selection of human talent for companies in the United States through the management of social networks

#### Sports Psychologist - Internship Jan 2021 - Dec 2021

-Military Sports Federation

Responsible of interviews and information verification through calls or chat, profiling and filtering through needs identification and psychological intervention programs development, interpretation and reporting results.

### Researcher - Scientific Article Publication March 2019 - Dic 2021

Universidad El Bosque

In charge of interviews, focus groups, review and analysis of scientific papers and psychological tests application, production and publication of a scientific article and participation as speaker in academic events.

# **SKILLS**

#### Languages

- English level B2
- · Native Spanish

#### Soft skills

- Adaptability
- Time management
- Leadership
- Communication skills
- Work ethic
- Problem Solving
- · Critical Thinking
- Interpersonal Skills
- Organization

#### Hard Skills

- Microsoft Office Package
- · Counseling and guidance
- Human Talent Management
- Recruitment and selection
- Test application
- Information analysis
- · Interview skills